Oh, fuck. Oh, fuck! Fuck!
- Are you sure it's him?
- I saw him hit the pavement.
Maruyama-san. Before Nakahara fell,
I saw Tozawa enter the building.
- Do you have photos of that?
- No. But he was there.
Fine. We'll include that detail.
Start dictating.
Noboru Nakahara...
...long time kaicho...
...of Kansai-based...
Answer me.
What were you looking
for in my study?
Nothing. I was curious to see
where you live, where you work.
Don't lie to me.
- I'm not lying to you.
- I'm not a stupid man.
I'm not...
I think I'm gonna just...
Oh, okay. What... what the fuck?
What's on this?
Did you photograph
my blueprints?
I don't understand.
Of what use is my work to you?
My club is half-owned
by the yakuza.
They found out about your project.
They asked me to get the information.
I said I would if they give me
the club free and clear.
So you did it
for yourself.
Yes. And for the girls, too.
To protect them.
I see.
"For the girls."
And my career gets ruined
in the process.
You can sleep on the couch.
It's too late to drive you home.
We'll discuss this tomorrow.
Gokurosan.
Katagiri-san.
How'd you hear?
I got a call. You?
I was in the office late and heard
the local station call it in.
I thought I recognized
the address.
- Witnesses?
- None.
He left a note in the penthouse.
No signs of struggle.
You buy it?
Even thugs come to the end
of their ropes.
It's not impossible.
So, Tozawa take over
the entire Kansai operation?
Hold on. I need a second.
No stopping. We keep moving.
What's your fucking problem?
My problem?
We've been walking all night in the
fucking snow with no idea where we are.
You're always stressing
about the little things.
We still got the money, right?
So we're doing fine.
"Doing fine"?
Are you serious?
What the hell is wrong with you?
Watch your tone!
I'm your kashira. Show respect.
Is something the matter?
My friend's hurt.
We need a ride.
I'm sorry, but we don't
have room.
We need a ride. I promise
my friend will behave.
But if you say no...
Come with me.
Masa-san, I am so sorry.
I won't tell them what I saw.
I'll say you caught me first,
that I couldn't find anything.
Ishida will have to accept that.
And what if you do not provide
Ishida with the location?
- What will he do to you?
- That's not your problem.
I got myself into this mess.
I'll get myself out.
There's another project
I'm working on.
Early stages.
If Ishida bought surrounding
properties there instead,
he could make
a significant return.
But you'd still be ruined.
Maybe not. Unlike Shimbashi,
this one is a private venture.
If there was a run on nearby
real estate,
the owners would profit.
And likely ask no questions.
If we convinced Ishida to accept this,
you could keep your club...
and I could I keep my job.
What if I could get someone
I know to publish the location
of your project in the press?
Wouldn't that make the Shimbashi
information worthless?
And then...
I could make my proposal
of a valuable replacement.
Why are you helping me?
I know what it is
to need forgiveness.
Thank you
for the call last night.
It was smart of you
not to talk to anyone else.
Of course.
You know there's no way
that Nakahara jumped, right?
I just wish I would've gotten
a picture
of Tozawa entering the building.
That fucker never came back out.
I will get back to you
with anything we learn.
And by "we," you mean
that female detective
who sent me
packing the other day?
How's that working out? She's like your
new partner or something?
- It is working fine.
- Great.
But we're still a thing, right?
Starsky & Hutch.
- Which of us is Starsky?
- Me, obviously.
I do not think so.
Thank you for keeping the fires
burning while I was away.
Nakahara was my father's
brother-in-law.
Of course.
That's why you're being so sullen.
You are in mourning.
In mourning that you did not
consult me.
We are on the verge of something
unprecedented.
Nakahara-san was in the way.
Not that it is any of your business.
It is my business.
My family's business.
Nakahara understood the need
for boundaries.
Between our legitimate businesses
and your questionable ones.
Not to mention
the side arrangements
you make for yourself
which threaten all of us.
I am going to go
if you lecture me.
In your absence,
I have continued
to cultivate relationships.
With those who will help bring
your plans to fruition.
I should be the one to continue
the conversation.
What are you afraid of?
That I'll embarrass your precious family?
Without my family,
you would still be nothing,
as you were when I met you...
Enough.
- I will not permit such disrespect.
- Neither will I.
Enough, woman.
Next, I would like to explain
about the suicide
from a high-rise apartment building
in 6-11-3 Yotsuya, Shinjuku-ku,
at around 9:20 pm last night.
The deceased was
Noboru Nakahara,
kaicho of a Kansai-based gumi.
He left a suicide note.
Authenticated.
There was an anonymous call
made to the police.
Does the building have a back door
by which an assailant could flee?
Suicide. Note. Authenticated.
- Are there cameras in the lobby?
- They weren't on.
Next question.
What did the suicide note say?
We will not disclose it in consideration
of the bereaved family's feelings. Next.
Any witnesses?
The first person to discover
the body was a neighbor.
Who heard a loud noise.
Your gaijin is smarter
than he looks.
If Tozawa has returned,
he must be our next target.
Agreed.
I should be able to get a
thirty-day wiretap approved
for Tozawa's offices
and hotel suite.
- You really think it'll be useful?
- Maybe we'll get lucky.
If you don't mind sitting
in a telecom basement
with a bureaucrat,
checking every call.
What is it?
Several months ago,
Tozawa threatened to kill my family and me
if I ever investigated him again.
I should have told you,
but there were plenty of other
gumis to go after.
So I did not.
Have you told headquarters
about these threats?
No.
I'm not sure who to trust
there anymore.
I'll make sure your family's protected.
HQ doesn't have to know.
We'll have you assigned to
a case unconnected to Tozawa...
As far as anyone knows.
After all, Detective,
you're not much good to me dead.
- Were you here for the press conference?
- I was hoping to run into you.
We need to talk.
My team found something about
the topic we were discussing.
One of my reporters has been
looking into Kazushin Holdings.
A series of corporations
owned by Kazuko Tozawa.
His wife?
All legitimate businesses.
At least on paper.
We found out they're a major donor
to several Nationalist political groups.
So the Tozawas are right-wingers.
No surprise.
True. But...
The surprise was that Baku is an active
member of one of the groups they fund.
Baku is on Tozawa's payroll?
I hate the guy, but I doubt it.
But maybe sometimes
he looks away.
Or does things
behind the scenes.
Like getting rid of a videotape.
And it's for sure that this complex
is being built over Shimbashi Station?
Yep, I've seen the blueprints.
It won't be announced for a good year,
but that's where it's going.
- This anything to do with Ishida?
- Can you just do this for me?
Are you in trouble?
Fine.
I'll follow it up.
Kenji,
was that another highball glass?
- Please try to be more careful.
- I will.
What's up with you?
There's something I need
to tell you.
Tozawa's back in Tokyo.
I saw him at his lawyer's office
and I followed him to a medical
building in Minato-ku.
I'm gonna make him pay
for what he did. I'm not giving up.
Jake, I love you
for wanting to take him on,
but having a death wish
isn't sexy.
We had videotape
of his men killing Pol,
no consequences.
His men beat you up,
So, no, I'd rather not find out one day
that you just disappeared
and there will
be no consequences.
Did you miss me
while I was gone?
You were gone far too long.
I am so glad for your recovery.
Thank you for your loyalty
in my absence.
You seem happier, too.
In a way I haven't seen
in so long.
I was thinking of the very first
time we met.
After that runway show.
Where you captivated me.
You spoke of the house you were
going to buy your mother someday.
You were kind to take
any interest.
I was thinking about a trip to
the mountain house this weekend.
The weather is meant
to be lovely.
While we're there, we can discuss
the house for your mother.
Aren't you happy?
In every way.
They know the actual location
of where their project is being built?
Yeah. My source just called me.
They said Shimbashi.
Are they
in the Transport Office?
No, they're... in a different field,
but I trust them.
Maruyama-san?
Have the article ready
for tomorrow's edition.
I was thinking
Kurihira should do it.
You want to give away a scoop?
I think he could really use it.
You know, Baku's been riding
him really hard.
Fine.
And your request for your trip
to America was approved.
Oh, I'm just not sure, what with
everything going on, that I should go.
Jake, there will always be stories,
but you have only one family.
The Ministry will say "no comment,"
so you'll just need to bluff a little.
I see.
Make them think that you already
have proof of the location.
You just need confirmation.
But don't say the name.
- Okay.
- Okay?
Jake-san.
Thank you for this tip.
We gotta look out
for each other, right?
You got this.
What do we
tell Oyabun about Ota?
We didn't even get the "tools."
I may have a solution.
But if I do this, you will do
something for me.
What's the solution?
I have access to some "tools."
Ishida told you not to get them.
You told me not to, too.
But I've been gathering them.
We can say they're from Ota.
That's fucking brilliant.
You're as sneaky a fucker as me.
After we give these tools
to Oyabun...
You will stay away
from my brother.
Or I'll tell Oyabun what happened
in that cabin. Understand?
I like how you negotiate.
Could you off turn
this shitty music?
IMPERIAL BUILDING
Can I help you?
I'd like to make an appointment.
This clinic only takes
referrals.
I'll get one. Thank you.
May I use your restroom?
Out the door, one floor up.
What brought you here?
It is no secret the city plans to build
on an existing train station.
The Ministry does not comment
until a project is announced publicly.
To prevent real estate
speculation.
Yes, but I have a source that's
already provided the location.
I'm doing you the courtesy...
I have other meetings.
If you'll excuse me.
Hold on, please.
It's Shimbashi. Confirm it.
Give me time to speak
to my supervisor.
Here.
Soviet surplus.
Well, better than nothing.
By the way, the gaijin mama-san,
you fucked her, yeah?
Never fucked a gaijin.
Are they the same down there?
Are you serious?
Am I being too loud again?
We are taking them out.
Kashira,
can you give us a moment?
Fucking bitch!
It was temporary.
Doesn't matter.
It isn't really my club.
As you made perfectly clear.
No, no. It's actually two circles
going in opposite directions.
So, let me get this straight.
You're talking
about the Yamanote line
that makes the big circle
around Tokyo.
Yes.
The outer track runs clockwise.
The inner track,
counter-clockwise.
So, if you prefer foreign men,
we say you ride
"the outer track."
So, I'm a foreign man.
Well...
And if you stick
to native Japanese men,
you ride the "inner track,"
right?
Exactly.
Good to know.
So, I guess
you're a outer track man, huh?
Actually...
tonight was my first time
on that track.
Really?
Thank you.
What about you?
To be honest...
it's been a year
since I've been with anyone.
Really? Why?
I got tired of not liking
the people in my bed.
Thank you.
It was a big deal for me
to approach you at that party.
I haven't done that
in a long time.
You have a lot of lost time
to make up for.
If you can keep up.
So here's Tozawa's file, right?
And here are the files
of four other yaks.
Are you sure they are yakuza?
Dude, you know how many fanzines I read.
I know all their names.
And check this out.
On every file...
Liver disease.
"Illness of the trade."
We call that shokugoyo.
Yakuza live a life filled with alcohol,
shabu, and tattoo needles.
Do that long enough,
and you get liver disease.
Well, it seems Tozawa has it,
or did.
It's not something
they get over.
The Ministry of Transportation
and the Tokyo Metropolitan Government,
announce that a shopping center will be
built over Shimbashi Station.
The shopping center will contain more
than 20 restaurants and retail stores...
Did you know this was happening?
He said he was going to get back
to me with a comment.
And you trusted him?
Are you brain damaged?
Now you have no story.
- Everything went according to plan?
- Perfectly.
Good work.
Thank you.
May we never need these.
Nicely done.
Thank you.
Hayama.
Why are you limping?
Yes.
I was trying to keep up
with this young buck.
I fell hard. Pulled something.
I'm getting old.
Sato.
Stay.
Take a seat.
Did you see the news today?
No. We were traveling.
The Ministry of Transportation
announced early.
Now the property in that
vicinity will go for top dollar.
It is unfortunate that they
announced before Samantha
could get you the information.
No.
Or perhaps she had other plans
all along.
I just received a message
from her.
She and the architect requested
a meeting tonight.
At the club.
I want you there.
A lesson may have to be taught.
Another outgoing call.
Put it on speaker.
- Hello?
- Mother. I've asked you many times.
Don't send Mugito
any more money.
Kazuko, it's a grandmother's prerogative
to send her grandchild money.
Not if his mother
asks you to stop.
Non-salient.
This is pointless.
Tozawa's clearly not using
these lines for work.
So what do you suggest?
That's Tozawa's guy.
Let's go.
They're using burners.
You were right.
That'll cost us two weeks of time.
I'll put in the paperwork.
For?
A warrant for the phone company
to issue us the serial numbers.
How can I help you?
The man who just bought
the prepaid phones.
I need the serial numbers.
I can't.
It's against the law.
No.
You suspect that the phones will
be used in a crime.
You are reporting your suspicions
to the police. Aren't you?
Oh, yes.
And I'd like these as well, please.
- Hi! You wanna hit one?
- No.
I have a busy night, Meicho.
- What's so important?
- I got you something.
To thank you for taking care
of that kid in jail.
Just one?
One more favor
and then I give you the other.
What do yakuza do when they get
the "illness of the trade"?
If they have
a liver issue, they die.
Nobody gives organs
in Japan.
Oyabuns just give up and die?
I don't believe it.
Some try to fight it and go to Thailand.
There's a German doctor there.
Does an infusion thing.
With blood from young people.
Fucking weird.
Does it work?
For... about six months.
Then they die.
Thank you.
- They are cool, aren't they?
- Yeah. Not bad.
These are too small.
You should have checked.
Hey, wait, you got a little brother,
right? Give 'em to him.
Okay.
But you're still in debt to me.
Hey, you wanna hit one?
C'mon, five minutes.
You should practice more.
Thank you.
Akiro.
Mother?
What are you doing here?
I have been waiting
for your brother.
He has not called for days.
He will not answer his phone.
- I'm sure he's okay.
- Don't patronize me.
I spoke to his professor.
Kaito has been getting in fights.
He's in danger of being
expelled.
I know what Kaito wants.
To follow you. Do what you do.
Akiro.
Promise me, you'll keep him out
of your world.
Yes. I promise you.
How could you choose this life,
these killers,
over your own family?
I chose them when Father
threw me out.
Or have you forgotten that part?
I can't lose both my sons.
If he throws away his life,
it will be your fault.
Fix this.
Right? It's like this rose...
I think it's rose. I don't know.
I have no idea.
Ladies, listen up.
We have a big night tonight.
Important guest.
Is it Liam Gallagher?
It's not Liam Gallagher.
But I do need you all in top form.
- Aren't we always in top form?
- Tip-top form then.
Ten minutes.
Okay.
Samantha?
What happened
with your architect?
It's so complicated.
But I think tonight,
everything gets sorted.
No more Chihara-kai.
I'm offering Ishida a deal,
and if he takes it,
the club is mine
a hundred percent.
Samantha... be smart.
Yakuza do not give things back.
It won't work.
It has to work.
Okay.
Let me run the floor tonight.
Whatever you need,
I'm there for you.
Thank you.
Everything okay?
Is that how we
"look out for each other," Jake-san?
By stabbing me in the back?
- What are you talking about?
- You gave me shit advice, so I would fail!
Dude, I told you
not to say the actual name.
After you did that, the Ministry had
to announce. That's on you, Tin-Tin.
- My name is Kurihira!
- What is your problem?
I'm the only one around here who
helps you.
I didn't ask for your help.
I took the exam the same day
you did, and I outscored you.
Why are you even here?
Okay, Kurihira.
Keep up the good work.
No matter how this goes...
I'd like to take you
to dinner tomorrow.
A real date.
I don't think the mama-san
is supposed to date clients.
Just one client, who I'm very grateful to
and very attracted to.
When we arrive, have your two
men stay in the other car.
We don't need to call attention.
Yes, Oyabun.
Hayama did not tell me
the truth today.
He is unchanged.
Did you two steal those guns
from Ota?
No.
I broke my word
to you weeks ago.
I collected those guns
in my fear for our future.
I disobeyed you. Arrogantly
believing in my own judgement.
You disobeyed me,
but you did it
to protect your brothers.
One day, your judgement
will protect the Chihara-kai.
When you are its leader.
What about Hayama?
An oyabun cares for his men.
Respects civilians.
Keeps his word.
As you do.
If anything were to happen
to me...
I'm depending on you.
I thought you'd be pleased.
I am. Thank you.
Tozawa tried to blackmail
Minister Shigematsu.
When he failed
and couldn't get into the U.S.
for medical care,
he may have gone to Thailand.
For this temporary cure.
Six months to live.
That would be lucky.
For you and your family.
But if Tozawa only has six
months, why kill Nakahara?
This is all wishful thinking.
He did not come back
and kill Nakahara just to die.
We must keep digging.
What if they don't comply?
Yabuki, men are simple.
- What about the photos?
- I've arranged for them.
Welcome all.
Especially our brothers
from Kansai.
We are all brothers.
Sons of Father Nakahara.
His death brings
us together this evening.
He was a great man who led us to
the brink of a new era.
To Nakahara!
But Nakahara's time had passed.
Because you decided his time
had passed!
Transition is difficult.
But most of you understand
that our future glitters.
As long as you're our oyabun, right?
I'm glad you ask.
No, gentlemen,
I will not be your oyabun.
There will be no more oyabun.
Either we change,
or the police destroy us.
Our future,
our power and wealth,
will flow from something new.
I will not be your Oyabun.
I will be your President.
Tozawa Corporation will entitle
you all to dividends.
Payment from the top down.
You will never pay tribute
again.
And if we don't join you?
If you wish to live in Osaka, beating up
pachinko owners for small bills...
Be my guest.
Or go join another organization.
But you won't last long because the police
are breaking them all up.
That day is done, my brothers.
The police are devouring our
enemies for us, one by one.
It's the best show in town.
I don't want pachinko.
I don't want brothels. I don't
want junkies for customers.
I want to be in every boardroom
in Japan.
I want the airlines!
I want the Olympics!
I want the Nikkei!
I want all of it!
Because when you are big enough,
when you touch
all their money...
When you control the flowing
blood of this country...
They will never arrest you.
Gentlemen, we are not criminals.
We are the future.
President! Banzai!
Banzai!
He's a really good kid.
You're a natural with him.
He likes you.
Yeah, yeah.
Thank you for meeting with me.
I am told you have
a proposition.
I had some information that
I did not realize was of value to you.
But Samantha-san has explained
your loss.
You did not realize?
And knowing your disappointment,
I sought another opportunity for you.
A mixed-use development project.
It will be called
Forest Daikanyama.
I'm not in the habit of
accepting consolation prizes.
And those who try to cheat me,
pay dearly for it.
We would never cheat you.
This information will provide
a substantial revenue stream.
Don't talk to me like I'm
an idiot.
No disrespect has been intended.
If you were to inspect this,
I think you would see its value.
You will see to it that there are no more
surprise announcements...
Until my business is complete.
I will.
If we are surprised again,
you will be solely liable
for my costs.
I will.
In that case... we have a deal.
Give him a drink.
Thank you!
Sato!
Sato...
Don't get killed.
Oyabun.
Oyabun!